statusbook.net 2015-06-10

# PRIVACY POLICY

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site.

When login to our site using the facebook login button, you will need to give permission to do the following: Access basic information,Includes name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, and any other information you share with everyone, Access profile information:About Me, Birthday and Current City. email (or anonymously proxy email that facebook give as an option before you allow to use your email), post on your facebook Wall,  
You may, however, visit our site anonymously without login. you could always delete your self by removing our application from your facebook by enter our application page :[statusbook.net app](http://www.facebook.com/apps/application.php?id=158593734180159) and click **Remove App** on the left buttom side of the page. by doing so all your private information will be deleted.(exept statuses that you send that will become anonimous, if you want to delete them please contact us using the mail in the button of this page)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
by letting only people who login to the site the option to add content to our data.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.statusbook.net/

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 5.2.2011

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.statusbook.net/  
statusbook.net@gmail.com  
Privacy Policy Created by Free Privacy Policy
